Tracy Early papers, Inclusive: 1924-2005, Bulk: circa 1940-2005
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Magazine and Newspaper Articles, 1947-2005; 1
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 3), 1976, 1980, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 3), 1980, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 3), 1968, 1971, 1983, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 5), 1975, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 5), 1985 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 5), 1975, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (4 of 5), 1985 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (5 of 5), 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 5), 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 5), 1985 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 5), 1985 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (4 of 5), 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (5 of 5), 1985 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 3), 1985 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 3), 1985 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 3), 1985 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 3), 1985 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 3), 1985 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 3), 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 2), 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 2), 1984-1986, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 4), 1977-1984, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 4), 1986 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 4), 1986 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (4 of 4), 1984-1987 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 3), 1980, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 3), 1983, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 3), 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 3), 1982, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 3), 1982-1986 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 3), 1979, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 4), 1986 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 4), 1982, 1985-1987 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 4), 1986 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (4 of 4), 1983-1984, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 4), 1981, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 4), 1986-1988 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 4), 1986-1988 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (4 of 4), 1986 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 4), 1986 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 4), 1986 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 4), 1982, 1986, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (4 of 4), 1986 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 3), 1986, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 3), 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 3), 1985-1987, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 3), 1987 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 3), 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 3), 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 3), 1987 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 3), 1987 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 3), 1987 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 4), 1987 March (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 4), 1987 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 4), 1987 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (4 of 4), 1987 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 5), 1987 April (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 5), 1987 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 5), 1987 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (4 of 5), 1987 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (5 of 5), 1987 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 5), 1987 May (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 5), 1987 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 5), 1987 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (4 of 5), 1987 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (5 of 5), 1987 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 7), 1987 June (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 7), 1987 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 7), 1987 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (4 of 7), 1987 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (5 of 7), 1987 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (6 of 7), 1987 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (7 of 7), 1987 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 7), 1987 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 7), 1987 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 7), 1987 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (4 of 7), 1987 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (5 of 7), 1987 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (6 of 7), 1987 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (7 of 7), 1987 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 9), 1988 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 9), 1988 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 9), 1988 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (4 of 9), 1988 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (5 of 9), 1988 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (6 of 9), 1988 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (7 of 9), 1988 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (8 of 9), 1988 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (9 of 9), 1988 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 8), 1988 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 8), 1988 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 8), 1988 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (4 of 8), 1988 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (5 of 8), 1988 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (6 of 8), 1988 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (7 of 8), 1988 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (8 of 8), 1988 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 5), 1989 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 5), 1989 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 5), 1989 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (4 of 5), 1989 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (5 of 5), 1989 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Catholic News Service: (1 of 10), 1989 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Catholic News Service: (2 of 10), 1989 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Catholic News Service: (3 of 10), 1989 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Catholic News Service: (4 of 10), 1989 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Catholic News Service: (5 of 10), 1989 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Catholic News Service: (6 of 10), 1989-1991 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Catholic News Service: (7 of 10), 1989 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Catholic News Service: (8 of 10), 1989 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Catholic News Service: (9 of 10), 1989 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Catholic News Service: (10 of 10), 1989 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Catholic News Service: (1 of 15), 1990 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Catholic News Service: (2 of 15), 1990 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Catholic News Service: (3 of 15), 1990 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Catholic News Service: (4 of 15), 1990 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Catholic News Service: (5 of 15), 1990 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Catholic News Service: (6 of 15), 1990 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Catholic News Service: (7 of 15), 1990 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Catholic News Service: (8 of 15), 1990 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Catholic News Service: (9 of 15), 1990 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Catholic News Service: (10 of 15), 1990 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Catholic News Service: (11 of 15), 1990 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Catholic News Service: (12 of 15), 1990 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Catholic News Service: (13 of 15), 1990 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Catholic News Service: (14 of 15), 1990 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Catholic News Service: (15 of 15), 1990 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Catholic News Service: (1 of 9), 1990 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Catholic News Service: (2 of 9), 1990 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Catholic News Service: (3 of 9), 1990 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Catholic News Service: (4 of 9), 1990 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Catholic News Service: (5 of 9), 1990 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Catholic News Service: (6 of 9), 1990 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Catholic News Service: (7 of 9), 1990 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Catholic News Service: (8 of 9), 1990 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Catholic News Service: (9 of 9), 1990 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Catholic News Service: (1 of 9), 1991 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Catholic News Service: (2 of 9), 1991 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Catholic News Service: (3 of 9), 1991 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Catholic News Service: (4 of 9), 1991 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Catholic News Service: (5 of 9), 1991 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Catholic News Service: (6 of 9), 1991 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Catholic News Service: (7 of 9), 1991 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Catholic News Service: (8 of 9), 1991 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Catholic News Service: (9 of 9), 1991 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Catholic News Service: (1 of 7), 1991 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Catholic News Service: (2 of 7), 1991 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Catholic News Service: (3 of 7), 1991 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Catholic News Service: (4 of 7), 1991 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Catholic News Service: (5 of 7), 1991 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Catholic News Service: (6 of 7), 1991 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Catholic News Service: (7 of 7), 1991 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Catholic News Service: (1 of 14), 1992 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Catholic News Service: (2 of 14), 1992 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Catholic News Service: (3 of 14), 1992 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Catholic News Service: (4 of 14), 1992 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Catholic News Service: (5 of 14), 1992 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Catholic News Service: (6 of 14), 1992 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Catholic News Service: (7 of 14), 1992 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Catholic News Service: (8 of 14), 1992 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Catholic News Service: (9 of 14), 1992 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Catholic News Service: (10 of 14), 1992 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Catholic News Service: (11 of 14), 1992 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Catholic News Service: (12 of 14), 1992 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Catholic News Service: (13 of 14), 1992 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Catholic News Service: (14 of 14), 1992 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Catholic News Service: (1 of 9), 1993 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Catholic News Service: (2 of 9), 1993 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Catholic News Service: (3 of 9), 1993 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Catholic News Service: (4 of 9), 1993 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Catholic News Service: (5 of 9), 1993 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Catholic News Service: (6 of 9), 1993 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Catholic News Service: (7 of 9), 1993 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Catholic News Service: (8 of 9), 1993 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Catholic News Service: (9 of 9), 1993 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Catholic News Service: (1 of 9), 1994 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Catholic News Service: (2 of 9), 1994 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Catholic News Service: (3 of 9), 1994 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Catholic News Service: (4 of 9), 1994 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Catholic News Service: (5 of 9), 1994 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Catholic News Service: (6 of 9), 1994 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Catholic News Service: (7 of 9), 1994 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Catholic News Service: (8 of 9), 1994 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Catholic News Service: (9 of 9), 1994 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Catholic News Service: (1 of 14), 1995 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Catholic News Service: (2 of 14), 1995 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Catholic News Service: (3 of 14), 1995 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Catholic News Service: (4 of 14), 1995 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Catholic News Service: (5 of 14), 1995 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Catholic News Service: (6 of 14), 1995 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Catholic News Service: (7 of 14), 1995 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Catholic News Service: (8 of 14), 1995 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Catholic News Service: (9 of 14), 1995 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Catholic News Service: (10 of 14), 1995 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Catholic News Service: (11 of 14), 1995 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Catholic News Service: (12 of 14), 1995 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Catholic News Service: (13 of 14), 1995 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Catholic News Service: (14 of 14), 1995 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Catholic News Service: (1 of 13), 1996 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Catholic News Service: (2 of 13), 1996 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Catholic News Service: (3 of 13), 1996 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Catholic News Service: (4 of 13), 1996 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Catholic News Service: (5 of 13), 1996 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Catholic News Service: (6 of 13), 1996 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Catholic News Service: (7 of 13), 1996 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Catholic News Service: (8 of 13), 1996 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Catholic News Service: (9 of 13), 1996 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Catholic News Service: (10 of 13), 1996 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Catholic News Service: (11 of 13), 1996 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Catholic News Service: (12 of 13), 1996 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Catholic News Service: (13 of 13), 1996 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Catholic News Service: (1 of 13), 1997 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Catholic News Service: (2 of 13), 1997 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Catholic News Service: (3 of 13), 1997 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Catholic News Service: (4 of 13), 1997 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Catholic News Service: (5 of 13), 1997 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Catholic News Service: (6 of 13), 1997 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Catholic News Service: (7 of 13), 1997 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Catholic News Service: (8 of 13), 1997 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Catholic News Service: (9 of 13), 1997 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Catholic News Service: (10 of 13), 1997 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Catholic News Service: (11 of 13), 1997 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Catholic News Service: (12 of 13), 1997 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Catholic News Service: (13 of 13), 1997 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Catholic News Service: (1 of 14), 1998 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Catholic News Service: (2 of 14), 1998 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Catholic News Service: (3 of 14), 1998 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Catholic News Service: (4 of 14), 1998 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Catholic News Service: (5 of 14), 1998 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Catholic News Service: (6 of 14), 1998 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Catholic News Service: (7 of 14), 1998 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Catholic News Service: (8 of 14), 1998 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Catholic News Service: (9 of 14), 1998 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Catholic News Service: (10 of 14), 1998 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Catholic News Service: (11 of 14), 1998 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Catholic News Service: (12 of 14), 1998 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Catholic News Service: (13 of 14), 1998 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Catholic News Service: (14 of 14), 1998 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Catholic News Service: (1 of 18), 1999 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Catholic News Service: (2 of 18), 1999 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Catholic News Service: (3 of 18), 1999 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Catholic News Service: (4 of 18), 1999 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Catholic News Service: (5 of 18), 1999 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Catholic News Service: (6 of 18), 1999 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Catholic News Service: (7 of 18), 1999 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Catholic News Service: (8 of 18), 1999 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Catholic News Service: (9 of 18), 1999 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Catholic News Service: (10 of 18), 1999 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Catholic News Service: (11 of 18), 1999 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Catholic News Service: (12 of 18), 1999 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Catholic News Service: (13 of 18), 1999 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Catholic News Service: (14 of 18), 1999 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Catholic News Service: (15 of 18), 1999 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Catholic News Service: (16 of 18), 1999 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Catholic News Service: (17 of 18), 1999 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Catholic News Service: (18 of 18), 1999 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Catholic News Service: (1 of 10), 2000 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Catholic News Service: (2 of 10), 2000 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Catholic News Service: (3 of 10), 2000 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Catholic News Service: (4 of 10), 2000 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Catholic News Service: (5 of 10), 2000 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Catholic News Service: (6 of 10), 2000 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Catholic News Service: (7 of 10), 2000 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Catholic News Service: (8 of 10), 2000 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Catholic News Service: (9 of 10), 2000 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Catholic News Service: (10 of 10), 2000 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Catholic News Service: (1 of 7), 2001 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Catholic News Service: (2 of 7), 2001 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Catholic News Service: (3 of 7), 2001 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Catholic News Service: (4 of 7), 2001 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Catholic News Service: (5 of 7), 2001 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Catholic News Service: (6 of 7), 2001 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Catholic News Service: (7 of 7), 2001 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Catholic News Service: (1 of 6), 2002 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Catholic News Service: (2 of 6), 2002 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Catholic News Service: (3 of 6), 2002 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Catholic News Service: (4 of 6), 2002 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Catholic News Service: (5 of 6), 2002 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Catholic News Service: (6 of 6), 2002 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Catholic News Service: (1 of 5), 2003 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Catholic News Service: (2 of 5), 2003 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Catholic News Service: (3 of 5), 2003 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Catholic News Service: (4 of 5), 2003 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Catholic News Service: (5 of 5), 2003 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Catholic News Service: (1 of 4), 2004 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Catholic News Service: (2 of 4), 2004 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Catholic News Service: (3 of 4), 2004 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Catholic News Service: (4 of 4), 2004 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Catholic News Service: (1 of 4), 2005 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Catholic News Service: (2 of 4), 2005 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Catholic News Service: (3 of 4), 2005 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Catholic News Service: (4 of 4), 2005 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (1 of 9), 1982 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (2 of 9), 1982 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (3 of 9), 1982 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (4 of 9), 1983 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (5 of 9), 1981, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (6 of 9), 1981, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (7 of 9), 1979, 1981, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (8 of 9), 1983 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (9 of 9), 1983 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (1 of 7), 1984 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (2 of 7), 1984, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (3 of 7), 1984 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (4 of 7), 1984 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (5 of 7), 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (6 of 7), 1984 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (7 of 7), 1984 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (1 of 6), 1985 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (2 of 6), 1985 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (3 of 6), 1985 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (4 of 6), 1985-1986 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (5 of 6), 1986 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (6 of 6), 1986, 1989, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (1 of 5), 1987 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (2 of 5), 1987 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (3 of 5), 1987 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (4 of 5), 1987 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (5 of 5), 1987 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (1 of 7), 1988 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (2 of 7), 1988 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (3 of 7), 1988 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (4 of 7), 1988 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (5 of 7), 1989 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (6 of 7), 1989 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (7 of 7), 1989 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (1 of 10), 1990, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (2 of 10), 1991 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (3 of 10), 1991 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (4 of 10), 1992 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (5 of 10), 1992 (Box 49, Folder 5)